<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>OneStopStats Blog</title>
        <link>https://sebastian.proost.science/blog</link>
        <description>OneStopStats Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[3,2,1 .... Lift Off!]]></title>
            <link>https://sebastian.proost.science/blog/lift-off</link>
            <guid>https://sebastian.proost.science/blog/lift-off</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[We're excited to kick off OneStopStats, the newest website to help you understand statistical concepts with ease. Whether you're a PhD student looking to ace your research, a data enthusiast trying to level up your skills, or simply someone who's always been curious about statistics, OneStopStats is here to help.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We're excited to kick off OneStopStats, the newest website to help you understand statistical concepts with ease. Whether you're a PhD student looking to ace your research, a data enthusiast trying to level up your skills, or simply someone who's always been curious about statistics, OneStopStats is here to help.</p><p>So, what's the concept? Well, imagine having a wise old owl by your side, answering all your statistical questions in a clear and concise way. That's exactly what we want to be for you. Our website provides simple and brief explanations of various statistical concepts, making it easy for you to understand and apply them in your work.</p><p>Our goal is to make statistical concepts accessible to everyone, regardless of their background or expertise. No more confusing jargon, complex formulas, or lengthy explanations that put you to sleep. With OneStopStats, you'll learn statistical concepts in a fun and casual way, without sacrificing accuracy or depth.</p><p>So, what are you waiting for? Put on your thinking caps and join us in the world of statistics. Check out our website and let us know what you think. We're always looking for feedback and suggestions to improve.</p><p>Happy statistical learning!</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>onestopstats</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>